Just, uh, out of curiosity,
did he ever have a shot with you?
(Girl:)Are you insane?
The guy was wearing an eye patch.
- So then why did you...?
- He said that I could drive a car on Mars.
(Raj:)- Got it.
- Yeah.
(Leonard:)So can I see you again?
You're not done seeing me now.
LEONARD:
Hm.
(Leonard:)Cool.
[KEYS CLICKING]
(Howard:)Anything?
(Raj:)Actually, I was just checking my e-mail.
(Raj:)But, uh, no, the rover is not responding.
(Sheldon:)I believe the appropriate metaphor here
involves a river of excrement...
(Sheldon:)...and a Native American water vessel
without any means of propulsion.
Hang on, there's gotta be other options.
You could try calling AAA.
(Raj:)But based on NASA's latest timetable,
they won't get there for 35 years.
Plus, I understand you have to be next to
the vehicle with your card when they arrive.